<module>
	<rawname>soundlang</rawname>
	<repo>standard</repo>
	<name>Sound Languages</name>
	<version>13.0.24.7</version>
	<publisher>Sangoma Technologies Corporation</publisher>
	<license>GPLv3+</license>
	<licenselink>http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.txt</licenselink>
	<changelog>
		*13.0.24.7* Fixing FREEPBX-17433 Whoops error due to typo error in sprintf 
		*13.0.24.6* If there is an error and the mirror servers are different reset them back
		*13.0.24.5* Catch errors on invalid xml
		*13.0.24.4* FREEPBX-14426 cannot install swedish language
		*13.0.24.3* FREEPBX-14294 better output during errors
		*13.0.24.2* FREEPBX-13723 Sound Languages fails when outputting to multiple formats
		*13.0.24.1* Fix blank page issues if urls are not accessible
		*13.0.24* Add additional language and location names
		*13.0.23.6* Make OOBE look nicer
		*13.0.23.5* Add OOBE to select Timezones and languages
		*13.0.23.4* FREEPBX-13488 cant set global to custom, FREEPBX-13468 already installed not detecting on first install
		*13.0.23.3* Fix potential crash on upgrade
		*13.0.23.2* Require core
		*13.0.23.1* Require framework
		*13.0.23* FREEPBX-12949 Allow listing of all available languages
		*13.0.22* FREEPBX-13336 Install missing packages for installed languages on module updates
		*13.0.21* FREEPBX-13335 Fix issue with saving settings when no languages are installed
		*13.0.19* FREEPBX-13330 ISO language codes are incorrect for Hebrew and Turkish.
		*13.0.18* FREEPBX-13042 Show authors/licenses for prompts and redesign packages page
		*13.0.17* FREEPBX-12620
		*13.0.16* Check to see if sounds were previously installed before installing
		*13.0.15* FREEPBX-12606 Absolute paths used in some modules.
		*13.0.14* Use Zip not Tar for zip files
		*13.0.13* FREEPBX-12287 Display message on invalid upload
		*13.0.12* FREEPBX-12287 If there were no files uploaded during an upload alert the user
		*13.0.11* For custom languages allow uploading of files and archives
		*13.0.10* FREEPBX-11733 remember grid settings
		*13.0.9* Remove en_US Translations
		*13.0.8* Work around /tmp directory issue on FreeBSD by lidl
		*13.0.7* Spelling
		*13.0.6* FREEPBX-10131
		*13.0.5* FREEPBX-10521 Wrong update of language in Soung Language module
		*13.0.4* FREEPBX-10147 save placement and location in cookie
		*13.0.2* Describe console commands for the normal person
		*13.0.1* Proper language replacement usage
		*13.0.0beta6* Standardize look and feel
		*13.0.0beta5* Start supporting locations (e.g. en_GB) and add a few languages/locations
		*13.0.0beta3* Fix missing language names when language not already installed
		*13.0.0beta2* Fix error when no languages installed
		*13.0.0beta1* Add custom languages
		*13.0.0alpha1* First release
	</changelog>
	<category>Admin</category>
	<description>
		Management of sound prompt languages.
	</description>
	<depends>
		<module>framework ge 13.0.121</module>
		<module>core 13.0.114.2</module>
		<version>13.0.0</version>
	</depends>
	<oobe method="oobeHook" priority="150"/>
	<menuitems>
		<soundlang>Sound Languages</soundlang>
	</menuitems>
	<supported>
		<version>13.0</version>
	</supported>
</module>